Guide to the Ronald Magden Papers
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
Ronald Magden papers
approximately 1879-2003
University of Washington Libraries Special Collections Box 352900 Seattle, WA 98195-2900
5185
Magden, Ronald
28.27 cubic feet 34 boxes
Historian, professor, and author from Tacoma, Washington
Labor historian, professor, and author from Tacoma, Washington. Magden researched and wrote several books, mainly in partnership with labor organizations in Tacoma and Seattle. Magden's books include The working waterfront: The story of Tacoma's ships and men, Furusato: Tacoma-Pierce County Japanese, 1888-1977, A History of Seattle Waterfront Workers, 1884-1934, Mukashi, mukashi =: Long, long ago: The first century of the Seattle Buddhist Church, and The working longshoreman. Materials from the research for most of these books comprise the collection
WASHINGTON LONGSHOREMEN. In the last two decades of the 19th century longshore labor organizations on the Pacific Coast were in flux, with several charters for local labor organizations appearing, disappearing and re-affiliating under various associations. This lasted into 1902, when the International Longshoremen’s Association (ILA) became the dominant labor organization in Washington ports until 1937. In that year, several ILA locals re-chartered themselves under the International Longshoremen’s and Warehousemen’s Union (ILWU). This reorganization was a response to the growing movement towards industrial unionism. The ILWU had chosden to affiliate with the newly formed Congress of Industrial Unions (CIO), while the ILA kept its ties to the craft union oriented American Federation of Labor (AFL). Seattle ILA local 38-12 was included in this reorganization; it became and remains ILWU local 19. Companies employing waterfront labor also organized to counter the forces in labor. 1908 saw the formation of the Waterfront Employers’ Union, which in 1920 changed its name to the Waterfront Employers of Seattle. In 1934 a statewide organization – the Waterfront Employers of Washington – appeared. This was followed by the creation of the Waterfront Employers’ Association of the Pacific Coast in 1937. Also present during this time was the Northwest Waterfront Employers’ Association – which included companies from all over the Pacific coast of the U.S. and Canada. The 1910’s saw a number of waterfront labor disputes and a major strike in 1916. This period of time was a peak in labor activity and organization, due in a great part to the local influence of the Industrial Workers of the World (“Wobblies”) and to the continuing global influence of the Russian Revolution. The next and largest west-coast waterfront strike took place in 1934 in the midst of the Great Depression. This labor action was a general strike of all types of waterfront labor in all of the major west-coast ports. During this strike tensions between the strikers and the employers, scabs and police escalated to violent clashes, including the infamous “Bloody Thursday” (July 5, 1934) confrontation in San Francisco.
WASHINGTON TEAMSTERS. Similarly, the collection of Teamster records also tracks the birth and development of regional (Washington) teamster, driver and chauffer unions, as well as the growth of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters. This organization was founded in the Midwest in the late 1800s. Its influence and reach grew in the last decades of that century, and in the early 1900s Teamster locals were forming on the west coast and throughout Washington state. Washington locals were involved in a 5-year strike 1910-15 and the various labor struggles of the 1930s – often affected by the efforts of longshore and maritime labor organizations.
NEWSPAPER UNIONS PUBLISHING CO.. The Newspaper Unions Publishing Company was formed in 1952 by striking Tacoma News Tribune workers. The company was created to publish a strike paper – The Tacoma Reporter – that was issued during June, July and August of that year. Following this strike, the company fell into inactivity.
Arranged in 4 accessions:
Accession no. 5185-001, Ronald Magden Collection, circa 1879-1988
Accession no. 5185-002, Ronald Magden Collection, Undated
Accession no. 5185-003, Ronald Magden Collection, 1930-2003 (bulk: 1971-2003)
Accession no. 5185-004, Ronald Magden Collection, circa 1983-1990
Materials created and collected by Ronald Magden, especially relating to research for books. See scope and content notes for individual accessions below.
Open to all users, but access to portions of the papers is restricted. Contact repository for details.
Magden, Ronald$vArchives; Historians$zWashington (State)$zTacoma$vArchives; College teachers$zWashington (State)$zTacoma$vArchives; Stevedores$zPacific States$xHistory$vSources; Labor unions$zPacific States$xHistory$vSources; Labor union members$zPacific States$vInterviews; International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union$xHistory$vSources; International Brotherhood of Teamsters$xHistory$vSources; Japanese Americans$zNorthwest, Pacific$xHistory$vSources; Tacoma (Wash.)$xHistory$vSources.; Personal correspondence; Business correspondence; Records (Documents); Interviews; Newsletters; Photographs; Ephemera; Minutes (Records); Collective labor agreements; Periodicals; Publications (documents); Research notes; Manuscripts (documents); Transcripts; Newspaper clippings; Membership lists; Business records; Financial records; Negatives (Photographs); Magden, Ronald$vArchives; Bridges, Harry,$d1901-1990; Bjorklund, John C.; Dawson, W. C.; Foisie, F. P.; Ringenberg, Merl Glen; Nelson, Burt; Hannon, Bruce; Labor Archives of Washington (University of Washington); International Longshoremen's Association. Pacific Coast District; Waterfront Employers of Seattle; Waterfront Employers of Washington; Newspaper Unions Publishing Company; Personal Papers/Corporate Records; Japanese Americans; Labor History; Labor Unions; Ships and Shipping; Washington (State); Seattle; Tacoma
- Ronald Magden collection, approximately 1879-1988; 5185-001; 10.4 cubic feet 12 boxes
  Transcripts and tape recorded interviews with longshoremen and teamsters. Photocopied minutes, reports, contracts, writings, membership records, clippings and secondary material collected and created by Magden, primarily for his book A History of Seattle Waterfront Workers (1998). The records relate especially to the activities of longshore workers and of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters on the West Coast. Much attention is paid to the matters of strikes, worker grievances, disputes and arbitrations, especially events that took place in the 1930s. Also covered is the history and development of the organizations themselves. These documents date from 1886 to the late 1990s, with a significant amount of material from the 1930s and 1940s.
  Material regarding the Teamsters accounts for a little more than 2 cubic feet of the accession, and dates from 1888 to 1996. The documents of the Newspaper Union Publishing Company make up a small fraction of the collection, and date from 1952-86.
  Many of the primary source materials are photocopies – including most of the minutes of the various organizations represented. However, original material can be found. Many of the arbitration files are originals, as is most of the correspondence. Much of the ephemera (especially in the Teamster subgroup) are originals. Almost everything in the Newspaper Unions Publishing Company subgroup is original material.
  A significant portion of this collection is Magden’s tapes and transcripts of interviews with local longshoremen who were active in the unions in the 1930s. Among those interviewed are John Mahoney, Shaun Maloney and Burt Nelson. There are also four transcripts of interviews with local teamsters, but the tapes are not included.
  Magden also collected the personal papers of a few individual longshoremen and union members. These papers include original material and give personal accounts of both daily longshore life in the 30s and 40s and the struggles and activities of longshore labor during this time.
  Open to all users, but access to portions of the papers restricted. Contact repository for details.
  Donor: Ronald E. Magden, July 12, 2000.
  - Biographical Features, 2000 (Box-folder 1/1)
  - Longshoremen Records, c. 1886- c.1993
    - Chronologies, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 1/2-3)
    - General Correspondence Of The White House (photocopies, FDR Library Papers), 1934-1936 (Box-folder 1/4)
    - Meeting Minutes, 1901-1938
      - AFL Convention, 1901 (Box-folder 1/5)
      - International Longshoremen, Marine and Transportworkers Association, 1907, Undated (Box-folder:oversize 9/1)
      - Joint Northwest Strike Committee, 1934 (Box-folder 1/6)
      - First Annual Convention of the Washington State Industrial Union Council, 1938 (Box-folder 1/7)
    - Transcripts Of Interviews, 1963-1989
      - Nelson, Burt, 1987 (Box-folder 5/1-5)
      - Enclosures in Burt Nelson Transcripts, 1963-1989, Undated (Box-folder 5/6-7)
      - Jenkins, Frank; Andy and Renee, 1987 (Box-folder 5/8)
      - Mahoney, Jack, 1987 (Box-folder 5/9)
      - Maloney, Shaun, 1987 (Box-folder 5/10)
      - Moisio, Wayne "Waino" and Esther, 1987 (Box-folder 5/11)
      - Prong, Larry, 1987 (Box-folder 5/12)
      - Wylie, Gordon S., 1987 (Box-folder 5/13)
      - Seattle Longshore Pensioners, 1986-1987, Undated (Box-folder 5/14-19)
      - Miscellaneous Notes, Undated (Box-folder 5/20)
    - Interview Tapes, c. 1987-c.1993 (Box-folder 6)
      - Bauman, Virgil; Maloney, Shaun, Undated
      - Hannon, 1993
      - Hannon/Lelli, Philip, 1992?
      - Mahoney, Jack, Undated
      - Maloney, Shaun, 1987-1992, Undated
      - Mink, Art, Undated
      - Vigil, David, Undated
    - Interview Transcripts On Diskette, c. 1986-c. 1987
      - Bauman, Virgil; Poth, Phil, Undated
      - Maloney, Shaun, Undated
      - Maloney, Shaun; Nelson, Burt; Prong, Lawrence; Jenkins, Frank, Undated
      - Moiso, Wayne;Wylie, Jack, Undated
      - Nelson, Burt, Undated
      - Nelson, Burt; Lelli, Philip, Undated
      - Seattle Longshore Pensioners, 1986-1987
      - Tacid/Unknown Pensioner, 1986
    - Reports, 1901-1968
      - Annual Report of U. S. Commissioner of Labor, 1901 (Box-folder 1/8)
      - Washington. Bureau of Labor. Biennial Reports, 1901-1918 (Box-folder 1/9)
      - “Report of the Civil Service Commission on the Work Of the Public Employment Office of Seattle for the Year 1911” (Box-folder 1/10)
      - National Adjustment Commission, 1918 (Box-folder:oversize 9/2)
      - Monthly Labor Review, 1924-1933 (Box-folder 1/11)
      - Washington Department of Labor and Industry, 1922-1941 (Box-folder 1/12)
      - “Longshore Productivity Study – Pacific Coast”, Pacific Maritime Association, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 1/13-14)
      - “Wage Chronology; Pacific Longshore Industry 1934-1970”, 1968 (Box-folder 1/15)
    - Writings Of Others, 1916-1995
      - “Pacific Coast Longshoring”, circa 1940s (Box-folder 1/16)
      - “The Saga of Longshore Jack and Waterfront Poems”, circa 1998? (Box-folder 1/17)
      - Theses, 1942-1952,1995, Undated (Box-folder 1/18-23)
      - Miscellaneous photocopied articles, 1916, 1934, 1975 (Box-folder 1/24-26)
    - Writings Of Others, Undated (Box-folder:oversize 9/3)
    - Arbitration Proceedings, 1934-1991
      - International Longshoremen’s Association, 1934-1942 (Box-folder 1/27-31)
      - International Longshoremen’s and Warehousemen’s Union, 1938-1941, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 1/32-35)
      - Miscellaneous, 1934-1943 (Box-folder 1/36-38)
    - Arbitration Awards, 1918 (Box-folder:oversize 10/1)
    - Arbitration Awards (listing), 1934-1940 (Box-folder 1/39)
    - Legislation, 1913 (Box-folder 1/40)
      - Workingmen’s Compensation Act, 1913
    - Index Of Worker Grievances And Procedures, 1960-1972 (Box-folder 1/41-46)
    - Lists, c. 1886-c.1976
      - Fatal Longshore Accidents, 1886-1976, Undated (Box-folder 2/1)
      - Company/Hall Gangs 1918-1919, Undated (Box-folder 2/2)
      - Strikers Reporting Sick, 1936 (Box-folder:oversize 12/1)
    - Bibliography, 1984 (Box-folder 2/3)
    - Handbooks, 1927; 1935 (Box-folder 2/4)
    - Leaflet, 1931 (Box-folder 2/5)
    - Notes Of Ronald Magden, Undated (Box-folder 2/6-8)
    - Notes, Undated (Box-folder:oversize 10/2)
    - Subject Series, 1886-1993
      - 1884
        - “History of Early Waterfront Organizations on Puget Sound”, Undated (Box-folder 2/9)
        - Constitution, Bylaws and Rules of Order of the Stevedores, Longshoremen and Rigger’s Union of Seattle, 1886 (Box-folder 2/10)
        - Articles of Incorporation of the Stevedores, Longshoremen and Riggers Union of Seattle, 1889 (Box-folder 2/11)
        - Lists – Members, Union Locals, Undated (Box-folder 2/12-13)
        - Journal Pages, 1892-1993 (Box-folder:oversize 9/4)
        - Union Cards, 1886-1988 (Box-folder 2/14)
        - Map of Yesler’s Wharf, 1896 (Box-folder 2/15)
        - Notes (Box-folder 2/16-17)
        - Clippings (Box-folder 2/18)
        - Clippings, 1885-1989 (Box-folder:oversize 10/3)
      - 1889, 1901-1905, Undated
        - Minutes of the Western Central Labor Union, 1903, Undated (Box-folder 2/19)
        - Minutes of the Seattle City Council, 1889 (Box-folder:oversize 9/5)
        - Correspondence of the Stevedores and Riggers’ Union of Puget Sound, 1889
        - Report from the Bureau of Labor, 1901-1902 (Box-folder 2/20)
        - Union Cards, I.L.A., 1903-1905 (Box-folder:oversize 10/4)
        - Seattle City Directory, 1901 (Box-folder 2/21)
        - Clippings, 1889-1903 (Box-folder:oversize 9/6)
      - Accidents, Safety and Compensation, 1928-1967, 1990 (Box-folder 2/22-30)
      - Accounts of the 1934 Strike (photocopies of previously published materials, theses, Magden’s notes), 1907-1984, Undated (Box-folder 2/31-44)
      - Bridges, Harry, 1916-1994 (Box-folder 2/45-50)
      - Bridges, Harry, 1937, 1991-1994 (Box-folder:oversize 10/5)
      - Collective Bargaining, 1945-1977 (Box-folder 2/51-61)
      - Industrial Workers of the World (I.W.W.), Undated (Box-folder 2/62-64)
      - Industrial Workers of the World, 1917-1919 (Box-folder:oversize 9/7-8)
      - Maritime Federation of the Pacific, 1935-1951, Undated (Box-folder 2/65)
      - Maritime Federation of the Pacific, 1934-1941 (Box-folder:oversize 10/6)
      - Port of Seattle, 1884-1986 (Box-folder 2/66-75)
    - Clippings (includes Notes), 1914-1990 (Box-folder 2/76-85,)
    - Clippings, 1895-1920; 1934-1990 (Box-folder 3/1-22)
    - Clippings, 1895-1920; 1934-1990 (Box-folder:oversize 9/9-18, 10/7-10, 11/1, 12/2-3)
    - Diskettes, Undated
      - Newspaper notes, Undated (Box-folder 6)
      - Officers, Charter members (chronologies), Undated (Box-folder 6)
  - Waterfront Employers Of Seattle, 1914-1957 (Box-folder 3/23-3/80)
    - Chronologies, Undated (Box-folder 3/23-24)
    - General Correspondence, 1916-1941 (Box-folder 3/25)
    - General Correspondence Of The Northwest Waterfront Employer’s Union, 1919-1934 (Box-folder 3/26)
    - Intraorganizational Correspondence – Waterfront Employers’ Association Of The Pacific Coast, 1920-1941 (Box-folder 3/27)
    - Memoranda, 1922 (Box-folder 3/28)
    - Meeting Minutes, 1908-1941
      - Meetings of General Membership, 1920, 1930-1937 (Box-folder 3/29-32)
      - Luncheon Meetings, 1933-1934 (Box-folder 3/33)
      - Annual Meetings, 1935-1940 (Box-folder 3/34)
      - Board of Trustees, 1925-1941 (Box-folder 3/35-40)
      - Finance Committee, 1934 (Box-folder 3/41)
      - Committee on Policy, 1934 (Box-folder 3/42)
      - Joint Executive Committee, 1921-1933 (Box-folder 3/43)
      - Joint Standard Practice Committee, 1931-1933 (Box-folder 3/44)
      - Joint Safety Committee, 1933 (Box-folder 3/45)
      - Joint Operating Committee, 1933 (Box-folder 3/46)
      - Joint Employment Committee, 1921, 1933 (Box-folder 3/47)
      - Joint Committee of Employees and Employers, 1933 (Box-folder 3/48)
      - Joint Executive Committee of Longshoremen, Truckers, and Waterfront Employers, 1933 (Box-folder 3/49)
      - Joint Committee of Steamship Owners And Local #18 Rigger’s and Stevedore’s Union, 1908 (Box-folder 3/50)
      - Special Committee for September 30th Program, 1935 (Box-folder 3/51)
      - Special Meetings, 1920-1941 (Box-folder 3/52-58)
      - Northwest Waterfront Employer’s Union, 1921-1925 (Box-folder 3/59)
      - Minutes of the Waterfront Council, 1931 (Box-folder 3/60)
      - Miscellaneous Minutes, 1921 (Box-folder 3/61)
    - Resolutions, 1935 (Box-folder 3/62)
    - Agreements, 1914-1916; 1934 (Box-folder 3/63-64)
    - Budget Files, 1935-1937; Undated (Box-folder 3/65)
    - Reports, 1920-1930
      - Employment Committee, 1920-1922 (Box-folder 3/66)
      - Annual, 1930, Undated (Box-folder 3/67)
    - Speeches And Writings, 1920-1937 (Box-folder 3/68-71)
    - Writings Of Others, 1957; Undated (Box-folder 3/72-73)
    - Petition Pre-1934, Undated (Box-folder 3/74)
    - Lists, 1935; Undated (Box-folder 3/75)
    - Notes
      - Of Frank P. Foisie [Head of Waterfront Employers Association], 1920 (Box-folder 3/76)
      - Of Ronald Magden, Undated (Box-folder 3/77)
    - Clippings, 1904-1934 (Box-folder 3/78)
    - Subject Series, 1919-1922
      - Hiring and Employment, 1921-1922 (Box-folder 3/79)
      - Rifles for Russia (labor stoppage), 1919 (Box-folder 3/80)
  - Waterfront Employers Of Washington, 1911-1988 (Box-folder 3/81-4/8)
    - Historical Features, c. 1947 (Box-folder 3/81)
    - Articles Of Incorporation, 1940 (Box-folder 3/82)
    - Bylaws, 1940 (Box-folder 3/83)
    - General Correspondence, 1936-1947
      - Coast Committee For the Shipowners, 1936 (Box-folder 3/84)
      - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union (ILWU) Local 1–19, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 4/1)
      - Tait Stevedoring Co., 1946 (Box-folder 4/2)
      - Miscellaneous, 1941, 1946
    - Agreements, 1931-1947 (Box-folder 4/3)
    - Welfare Plan (ILWU And Pacific Maritime Association), 1950 (Box-folder 4/4)
    - Hearings, 1934 (Box-folder 4/5)
    - Lists – Longshoremen Wages, Undated (Box-folder 4/6)
    - Clippings (Includes Notes), 1936-1941 (Box-folder 4/7)
    - Subject Series – Biographies Of Prominent Merchants, 1911-1988 (Box-folder 4/8)
  - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union, Local 1-19 (Seattle), c. 1946- c. 1987 (Box-folder 4/9-4/27)
    - Notes On Minutes Of International Longshoremen's Association (ILA) Local 38-22, 1918-1937, c. 1987 (Box-folder 4/9-12)
    - Notes On Minutes Of ILWU Local 1-19, 1937-1985, c. 1987; (Formerly known as ILA Local 38-22) (Box-folder 4/13-21)
    - General Correspondence (Box-folder 4/22)
      - re: Waterfront Employer's Association (WEA) and the Fred LaPlant claim, 1946
    - Intraorganizational Correspondence – ILWU
      - re: Ship, Dock, and Walking Bosses, 1946 (Box-folder 4/23)
      - re: Pinkerton Detective Agency, 1946 (Box-folder 4/24)
        - Miscellaneous, 1946 (Box-folder 4/25)
    - Bulletin, Undated (Box-folder 4/26)
    - Lists – Roster Of Delegates To 8th Biennial Convention, 1949 (Box-folder 4/27)
  - International Longshoremen's Association, Pacific Coast District, 1916-1935 (Box-folder 4/28-4/36)
    - General Correspondence, 1922-1935 (Box-folder 4/28)
    - Minutes
      - District Conventions, 1916-1922 (Box-folder 4/29-32)
      - District Conventions, 1921-1931 (Box-folder:oversize 9/19-20)
      - Executive Board, 1935 (Box-folder 4/33)
    - Agreements, 1920 (Box-folder 4/34)
    - Court Papers, 1920 (Box-folder 4/35)
    - Lists, circa 1920’s (Box-folder 4/36)
  - Portland Longshoremen, 1879-1991 (Box-folder 4/37-4/51)
    - Articles Of Incorporation For Stevedores, Longshoremen And Rigger’s Union, 1879 (Box-folder 4/37)
    - Telegram, 1934 (Box-folder 4/38)
    - Minutes
      - General Longshoremen’s Association # 265 (a.k.a. Pacific Coast Association of Longshoremen Local #6), 1901-1908 (Box-folder 4/39-42)
      - ILA Local 38-6, 1918-1919 (Box-folder 4/43-44)
      - ILA Local 38-78, 1931 (Box-folder 4/45)
    - Transcripts Of Hearings, Undated (Box-folder 4/46)
    - Writings Of Others, 1984, 1991, Undated (Box-folder 4/47)
    - Lists, Undated (Box-folder 4/48)
    - Notes Of Ronald Magden, Undated (Box-folder 4/49)
    - Clippings, Undated (Box-folder 4/50)
    - Ephemera, 1991 (Box-folder 4/51)
  - McAlpin, Robert, 1926-1992 (Box-folder 4/52-4/59)
    - Biographical Features, Undated (Box-folder 4/52)
    - Diary, 1926 (Box-folder 4/53)
    - General Correspondence Of Others
      - re: McAlpin’s Naval Service, 1943-1945 (Box-folder 4/54)
      - re: McAlpin’s Death, 1948-1950 (Box-folder 4/55)
      - re: McAlpin Baby Books, 1992 (Box-folder 4/56)
    - Awards, 1945, Undated (Box-folder 4/57)
    - Ephemera, 1944, Undated (Box-folder 4/58)
    - Subject Series – McAlpin, Marguerite, 1957-1973, Undated (Box-folder 4/59)
  - Hannon, Bruce
    - General Correspondence, 1955-1996 (Box-folder 4/60)
    - Case Files – FBI, 1942 (Box-folder 4/61)
    - Writing – “a Window On The Thirties”, circa 1990’s (Box-folder 4/62)
    - Union Cards, 1933-1938 (Box-folder 4/63)
  - Nelson, Burt
    - Outgoing Letters, 1938-1949 (Box-folder 4/64)
    - Arbitration Opinion, 1965 (Box-folder 4/65)
    - Writings, 1971 (Box-folder 4/66)
    - Writings Of Lonnie Nelson (Daughter of Burt Nelson), 1950, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 4/67)
  - Gus Rystad
    - Outgoing Letters, 1970-1992 (Box-folder 4/68)
    - General Correspondence
      - Bridges, Harry, 1977, 1987 (Box-folder 4/69)
      - Hall, Gus, 1970 (Box-folder 4/70)
      - Irene _____, 1991
      - Meyers, George, 1989
    - General Correspondence Of Others, 1970, Undated (Box-folder 4/71)
    - Writings, 1973, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 4/72)
    - Writings Of Others, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 4/73)
    - Subject Series – Bridges, Harry, 1990-1991 (Box-folder:oversize 9/21)
    - Clippings, 1992, Undated (Box-folder:oversize 9/22)
  - Teamster Records
    - Organizational Features, 1991, Undated (Box-folder 7/1)
    - Historical Features – “the Teamsters’ Story”, Undated (Box-folder 7/2)
    - Chronologies, Undated (Box-folder 7/3)
    - General Correspondence Of Ronald Magden, 1988-1996 (Box-folder:oversize 9/23)
    - Contracts, c. 1988 (Box-folder 7/4)
    - Court Rulings, 1962, 1989 (Box-folder 7/5-6)
    - Writings, 1959, Undated (Box-folder 7/7-8)
    - Census Record, 1900 (Box-folder:oversize 11/2)
    - Lists - Members, Undated (Box-folder 7/9)
    - Notes Of Ronald Magden, Undated (Box-folder 7/10)
    - Notes Of Ronald Magden “historical Evolution Of Seattle Teamster Unions”, Undated (Box-folder:oversize 11/3)
    - Exhibit Catalogue (and Enclosures) (Box-folder 7/11)
      - “Teams Trucks Tri-Motors and Trains – the Transporation
      - Paintings of Ollie C. Ziegler”, 1991
    - Membership Manual, circa 1985 (Box-folder 7/12)
    - Newsletter – Western Conference Of Teamsters, 1990 (Box-folder 7/13)
    - Bibliographies, Undated (Box-folder 7/14)
    - Maps, Undated (Box-folder 7/15)
    - Chart, 1991, Undated (Box-folder 7/16)
    - Photographs And Negatives, 1919, 1928, 1937, Undated (Box-folder 7/17)
      Photographic prints in this accession were removed and moved to the Ronald Magden Photograph Collection, Photo Collection #1106.
    - Photographs, 1941-1942; Photographic prints in this accession were removed and moved to the Ronald Magden Photograph Collection, Photo Collection #1106. (Box-folder:oversize 11/4)
    - Photographs, 1941-1942; Photographic prints in this accession were removed and moved to the Ronald Magden Photograph Collection, Photo Collection #1106. (Mapcase Map case Drawer 1)
    - Subject Series – Working Women, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 7/18)
    - Ephemera, 1991, Undated (Box-folder 7/19-21)
    - Portfolio (empty, Contained Madgen’s Notes), Undated (Box-folder 7/22)
    - Clippings